<resources>
    <string name="app_name">About me</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="gym_text">I started going to the gym about a year ago, mainly because my girlfriend at the time told me I would be so hot with muscles. Whether or not she was right I am glad I listened because now I am in better shape, and feel how a teenager should (invincible). I really only started getting kind of serious about it at the beginning of summer though; Meaning, that I started going for longer with real goals and going 6 days a week. Over all I am very proud of myself that I actually began enjoying it, I just feel in a better place with it all in all. plus I am getting super yolked.</string>
    <string name="skating_text">Skateboarding is one of my favorite pass times, I am horrible at it though don’t be mistaken. I mainly do more street stuff, because I am terrified by the bowl, like grinding, nollies, ollies, nose grinds, and stalls; However, I am not one of those skaters who: eats, breathes, and lives skating. The skating In my opinion is just my stereotypical punk coming out, we will come back to that later. </string>
    <string name="working_text">I work at Einstein bagels near where I live down In Draper. The people are super cool, and the hours are great for a high schooler. (3 to 6 on weekdays) Most my friends work there so It is basically a place to hangout with my friends in all reality. Plus the food isnt too bad either and I get free bagels so needless to say I have trouble holding back my hunger there. </string>
    <string name="computer_text">During the summer this year for the first time in my life I built a computer. I was pretty scared because I had never even done anything like it before and all I had were the manuals and youtube, so some great teachers. After 8 hours of building went by without eating or drinking I finally turned it on! I am pretty happy with myself, because if you had told me I would do that even months earlier I would have called you stupid and said I wouldn’t even dare to try. Either way It was super fun and I hope to get the chance again sometime. (Above is the picture of my computer.)</string>
    <string name="music_text">Music Is a pretty big part of my life, It entertains me more than most things would, for longer. I have noticed it also helps me study and work harder, when it is ambient music,  and faster. I have to say of all the genres out there I like rock or anything similar; However, my favorite genres are Punk, Rock, Metal, Ska (Yes that is how you spell it but is pronounced skaw) I play the guitar, so I feel that this really just adds to my love of these genres.</string>
</resources>
